After copying over the assets, updating the launcher icon
in the Android manifest, and adding the Helper methods
to the Utility class, we need to modify the
DetailFragment and ForecastAdapter classes. In the DetailFragment class, in the
onLoadFinished method, we read the weather condition code from
the cursor, then we pass it into the Utility
Helper method to get the colored icon for setting
onto the image view. In the detail fragment on load
finish method, we read the weather condition code from the cursor.
Then we pass this into the Utility helper method, to get
the Resource ID for the colored icon, in order to set
it onto the Image View. The forecast adapter change is a
little trickier because we want to use the colored icon for the
today layout. And we want to use a grey icon for
the other days. In order to distinguish between the other two,
we call get item view type given the current cursor position.
If the view type is today, then we get the weather condition
code from the cursor. Then we get the resource ID for the
colored image from the helper method. And then we set that onto
the image view. If the view type is for a future day, then
we read the whether condition code from the cursor. Then we pass
it into the helper method to get the resource ID the gray
icon and then we send that on to the image view. If
you previously hard coded an image into the layout, then you should remove
that value now. Otherwise, on app launch, it will load
up the placeholder image and then flash to the actual
icon. Now that the wire frame implementation for the phone
UI is pretty much complete, let's look at the tablet UI.